AoM Records 5289
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series SERIES I. ADMINISTRATIVE RECORDS
  - Sub-Series C. EXECUTIVE OFFICERS.
    - Bedeian, A., 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 67)
      All-Academy Task Force on Ethics
    - Bedeian, A., 1988 (Box 6, Folder 68)
      Associate Secretary-Treasurer Search Committee, correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1987-1989 (Box 6, Folder 69)
      Management Practitioners' Task Force, correspondence and survey
    - Bedeian, A., 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 70)
      Task Force on Outcome Measurement, meeting agenda, August 1989 and correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 71)
      Regional Divisions, general correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 72)
      Midwest Division of the Academy of Management
    - Bedeian, A., 1988 (Box 6, Folder 73)
      Southern Management Association, or the Southern Division of the Academy of Management
    - Bedeian, A., 1988 (Box 6, Folder 74)
      Southwest Division of the Academy of Management
    - Bedeian, A., 1987 (Box 6, Folder 75)
      Western Division of the Academy of Management
    - Bedeian, A. (Box 6, Folder 76)
      Professional Divisions/Interest Groups, correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 77)
      Divisional/Interest Groups, financial accounts, October 1, 1987 June 13, 1988
    - Bedeian, A., 1989 (Box 6, Folder 78)
      Business Policy and Planning Division, correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 79)
      Careers Division, correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 80)
      Entrepreneurship Division, correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1988 (Box 6, Folder 81)
      Health Care Administration Division, correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1988 (Box 6, Folder 82)
      Managerial Consultation Division, correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 83)
      Management Education Division, correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1988 (Box 6, Folder 84)
      Management History Division, correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 85)
      Management History Division, Oral History Video Project, proposal
    - Bedeian, A., 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 86)
      Organizational Behavior Division, correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1987-1990 (Box 6, Folder 87)
      Organizational Communications Division, correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1987 (Box 6, Folder 88)
      Organizational Information Systems Special Interest Group, correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1987 (Box 6, Folder 89)
      Personnel/Human Resources Division, correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1987 (Box 6, Folder 90)
      Power, Negotiation, and Conflict Management Interest Group, correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 91)
      Production/Operations Management Division, correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1988 (Box 6, Folder 92)
      Research Methods Division, correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 93)
      Women In Management Division, correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1987-1990 (Box 6, Folder 94)
      Fellows Group, correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1987-1989 (Box 6, Folder 95)
      Sigma Iota Epsilon, correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1988-1990 (Box 6, Folder 96)
      Awards Committee, correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 97)
      Budget for fiscal year 1988 89, correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 98)
      student dues and registration fees, correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1989 (Box 6, Folder 99)
      miscellaneous financial records
    - Bedeian, A., 1977 (Box 6, Folder 100)
      Academy of Management Review (AMR) Editorial Review Board, correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1988-1990 (Box 6, Folder 101)
      AMR, correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1987 (Box 6, Folder 102)
      AMR, Annual Meeting, Call for Papers
    - Bedeian, A., 1987 (Box 6, Folder 103)
      Proposal for literature databases for the Academy of Management Journal (AMJ) and AMR
    - Bedeian, A., 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 104)
      AMJ, correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1987-1989 (Box 6, Folder 105)
      Academy of Management Executive (AME), correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1988 (Box 6, Folder 106)
      AME, readership survey and recommendations, report by The Promotion Network
    - Bedeian, A., 1988 (Box 6, Folder 107)
      AME, letter to increase subscriptions
    - Bedeian, A., 1989 (Box 6, Folder 108)
      AME, Editor-Designate search committee
    - Bedeian, A., 1989 (Box 6, Folder 109)
      AME, Editor nominations
    - Bedeian, A., 1988 (Box 6, Folder 110)
      Academy of Management Newsletter (Newsletter), correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 111)
      presidential profile for Newsletter
    - Bedeian, A., 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 112)
      Academy of Management Proceedings, correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1989 (Box 6, Folder 113)
      Academy of Educational Development, correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 114)
      Administrative Sciences Association of Canada (ASAC), correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1989 (Box 6, Folder 115)
      ASAC, Annual Conference Program
    - Bedeian, A., 1987 (Box 6, Folder 116)
      American Assembly of Collegiate Schools of Business (AACSB), correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1987 (Box 6, Folder 117)
      AACSB, Outcome Measurement Project, correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1988 (Box 6, Folder 118)
      American Association of University Professors, correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1988 (Box 6, Folder 119)
      American Council of Learned Societies, correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1988 (Box 6, Folder 120)
      American Psychological Society, correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1987 (Box 6, Folder 121)
      American Sociological Association, publications information
    - Bedeian, A., 1989 (Box 6, Folder 122)
      British Academy of Management, correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1989 (Box 6, Folder 123)
      The Organizational Behavior Teaching Society, correspondence
    - Bedeian, A. (Box 6, Folder 124)
      Organization Development Institute, correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1989 (Box 6, Folder 125)
      'Correct Practices' correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1990 (Box 6, Folder 126)
      correspondence re: drug use by professionals
    - Bedeian, A., 1979-1989 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation, correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      Management Week in America, correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      American Manager of the Year Award, sponsored by the National Management Association, presented during Management Week in America, correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1988 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      correspondence with meeting planning agencies
    - Bedeian, A., 1988 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      Responsibilities of Vice President and Program Chair, correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      Shigeo Shingo Prize for Manufacturing Excellence, correspondence and description
    - Bedeian, A., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      correspondence with Soviet consulting firm "Contact,"
    - Bedeian, A., 1988 (Box 7, Folder 8)
      invitations to Academy of Management (AOM) Service Recognition Receptions
    - Bedeian, A., 1986-1990 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      misc. correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1956 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      Masters Thesis of Franklin G. Moore, AOM President
    - Beyer, J., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      correspondence from 1987 Program Chair (A. Bedeian) used by Beyer in planning Annual Meeting
    - Beyer, J., 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 12)
      V.P. & Program Chairperson, general correspondence, includes a transmittal letter from Steve Kerr, dated August 18, 1988 referring to material Kerr sent to Beyer to aid her in planning 1989 Annual Meeting
    - Beyer, J., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 13)
      Annual Meeting, general correspondence
    - Beyer, J., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 14)
      Annual Meeting, 'Call for Papers,' correspondence
    - Beyer, J., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      Pre-Conference Workshops, correspondence
    - Beyer, J., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 16)
      Post-Convention Workshop Proposals
    - Beyer, J., 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      Local Arrangements Committee, correspondence
    - Beyer, J., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 18)
      Annual Meeting, correspondence with Washington Hilton & Towers
    - Beyer, J., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 19)
      Annual Meeting, All-Academy Catering, correspondence, menus, and costs
    - Beyer, J., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 20)
      Annual Meeting, Procedures for Divisional catering charges, correspondence
    - Beyer, J., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 21)
      Annual Meeting, Washington, D.C. Convention and Visitors Association, correspondence
    - Beyer, J., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 22)
      Annual Meeting, overflow hotels, correspondence and contracts
    - Beyer, J., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 23)
      Annual Meeting, audio-visual contractor, correspondence and proposals
    - Beyer, J., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 24)
      Annual Meeting, decorating contract, correspondence
    - Beyer, J., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 25)
      Annual Meeting, photography contract, correspondence
    - Beyer, J., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 26)
      Annual Meeting, proposed letter to exhibitors
    - Beyer, J., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 27)
      Annual Meeting, Meetings, Incentives, Conventions of America, Inc., (MICA), correspondence
    - Beyer, J., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 28)
      Annual Meeting, Convention Resume
    - Beyer, J., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 29)
      Annual Meeting, memos to division program chairs
    - Beyer, J., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 30)
      Annual Meeting, division program chairs, correspondence
    - Beyer, J., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 31)
      Annual Meeting, division session attendance forms
    - Beyer, J., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 32)
      Annual Meeting, Program, general correspondence
    - Beyer, J., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 33)
      Annual Meeting, All-Academy Program Sessions, proposals and correspondence
    - Beyer, J., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 34)
      correspondence re 1989 Program schedule conflicts
    - Beyer, J., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 35)
      Annual Meeting, Program additions and changes
    - Beyer, J., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 36)
      Annual Meeting, Program, printing costs
    - Beyer, J., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 37)
      Annual Meeting, guest speakers, correspondence
    - Beyer, J., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 38)
      Annual Meeting, Welcome and Conference Reminders
    - Beyer, J., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 39)
      Annual Meeting, showcase sessions proposals
    - Beyer, J., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 40)
      All-Academy Symposium Proposal: "Initiatives in Business Ethics"
    - Beyer, J., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 41)
      All-Academy Symposium in conjunction with The Minerva Education Institute
    - Beyer, J., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 42)
      All-Academy Symposium Proposal: "Babies and the Bottom Line"
    - Beyer, J., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 43)
      Program Summary by Academy Divisions
    - Beyer, J., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 44)
      Notes for future program chairpersons
    - Beyer, J., 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 45)
      Committee Assignments, handwritten notes and correspondence
    - Beyer, J., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 46)
      Media Relations Committee, correspondence re: 1989 Annual Meeting
    - Beyer, J., 1990 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Beyer, J. (Box 7, Folder 48)
      Nominating Committee, notes and correspondence, n.d.
    - Beyer, J., 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 49)
      Professional Division Review Committee, correspondence
    - Beyer, J., 1991 (Box 7, Folder 50)
      Publications Committee, notes and correspondence
    - Beyer, J., 1990 (Box 7, Folder 51)
      Scholarly Contribution and Terry Book Awards Committee, notes and correspondence
    - Beyer, J., 1991 (Box 7, Folder 52)
      Committee on the Status of Women, correspondence
    - Beyer, J., 1989-1991 (Box 7, Folder 53)
      Task Force Reports on Activities
    - Beyer, J., 1991 (Box 7, Folder 54)
      Management Practitioners' Task Force, correspondence
    - Beyer, J., 1990 (Box 7, Folder 55)
      Task Force on Outcome Measurement, correspondence
    - Beyer, J., 1987-1991 (Box 7, Folder 56)
      Task Force on Possible New Journal, correspondence
    - Beyer, J., 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 57)
      Advisory Board for the Academy Newsletter, correspondence
    - Beyer, J., 1990 (Box 7, Folder 58)
      Consulting Group on Academy Growth and Structure, correspondence and report
    - Beyer, J., 1990 (Box 7, Folder 59)
      Managerial and Organizational Cognition Interest Group, correspondence
    - Beyer, J., 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - Beyer, J., 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 61)
    - Beyer, J., 1988 (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - Beyer, J., 1987-1991 (Box 7, Folder 63)
      miscellaneous correspondence
    - Brown, A., 1957 (Box 7, Folder 64)
      correspondence
    - Cummings, L.L., 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 65)
    - Cummings, L.L., 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 66)
    - Cummings, L.L., 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 67)
    - Cummings, L.L., 1979 (Box 7, Folder 68)
      Annual Meeting, thank-you letters
    - Cummings, L.L., 1980 (Box 7, Folder 69)
      Academy of Management (AOM) Policy Statement on Awards
    - Cummings, L.L., 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 70)
      Status of Women Interest Group, correspondence, includes discussion of a proposal to create a Research on Women and Minorities Division
    - Davis, K., 1964 (Box 7, Folder 71)
      communication to the Academy membership
    - Davis, R.C., 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 72)
      File, includes original documents regarding the founding of the Academy; 1938 Annual Meeting program and correspondence; discussions of problems getting Academy started; handwritten document on funding from the Sloan Foundation
    - Davis, R.C., 1939-1942 (Box 7, Folder 73)
      File, includes original documents re: the Academy's early years, correspondence on membership issues, and a questionnaire on the Academy constitution
    - Davis, R.C., 1946-1947 (Box 7, Folder 74)
      File, includes correspondence regarding and program for "Renaissance Day," the 1947 Annual Meeting, was the first meeting after World War II; membership list, October 21, 1947
    - Davis, R.C., 1953 (Box 7, Folder 75)
      Nominating Committee
    - Davis, R.C., 1953 (Box 7, Folder 76)
      Special Committee on Membership. Correspondence re: reconciling the small, exclusive feel of the Academy in 1953, with the future of the Academy as an organization of academic professionals
    - Davis, R.C., 1954-1959 (Box 7, Folder 77)
      File, includes 1956 Annual Meeting program; Nominating Committee correspondence; discussion on the incorporation of the Academy, 1957; membership lists, 1958 59
    - Davis, R.C., 1959-1960 (Box 7, Folder 78-79)
      File, includes correspondence as 1959 60 chair of the Nominating Committee; ballots for 1959 elections; officer slate for 1960 elections; correspondence re: developing the Academy of Management (AOM) Journal and creating the Western Academy of Management
    - Davis, R.C., 1961-1962 (Box 7, Folder 80)
      File
    - Folts, F., 1953 (Box 7, Folder 81)
      Correspondence
    - Glueck, W., 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 82)
    - Glueck, W., 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 83)
    - Glueck, W., 1979 (Box 7, Folder 84)
      Report of the Task Force on Academy Governance and Professional Divisions Policy Committee
    - Goetz, B., 1955 (Box 7, Folder 85)
    - Presidential Newsletter, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 86)
    - Hellriegel, D., 1987 (Box 7, Folder 87)
      December, 1987 Board of Governors (BOG), correspondence
    - Hellriegel, D., 1988 (Box 7, Folder 88)
      April, 1988 BOG Meeting, agenda and correspondence
    - Hellriegel, D., 1986 (Box 7, Folder 89)
      Annual Meeting, Program Chair, correspondence
    - Hellriegel, D., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 90)
      Annual Meeting, program, correspondence
    - Hellriegel, D., 1987 (Box 7, Folder 91)
    - Hellriegel, D., 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 92)
      President-Elect, correspondence
    - Hellriegel, D., 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 93)
      President, correspondence
    - Hellriegel, D., 1987 (Box 7, Folder 94)
      Professional Divisions Review Committee
    - Hellriegel, D., 1987 (Box 7, Folder 95)
      Membership Survey
    - Hellriegel, D., 1988 (Box 7, Folder 96)
      Nominations, correspondence with the membership
    - Hellriegel, D., 1988 (Box 7, Folder 97)
      Eastern Academy of Management, correspondence
    - Hellriegel, D., 1987 (Box 7, Folder 98)
    - Hellriegel, D., 1988 (Box 7, Folder 99)
    - Hellriegel, D., 1987 (Box 7, Folder 100)
    - Hellriegel, D., 1984 (Box 7, Folder 101)
      Proposed Academy of Management Executive, correspondence
    - Hicks, H., 1971 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Hicks, H., 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Jamison, C., 1936-1953 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Kast, F., 1975 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      Managerial Education Division, correspondence
    - Kast, F., 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Kast, F., 1976-1978 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      Academy of Management (AOM) Journal and AOM Review, correspondence
    - Kerr, S., 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Kerr, S., 1988 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Kerr, S., 1988 (Box 8, Folder 9)
      Annual Meeting, handwritten notes
    - Kerr, S., 1988 (Box 8, Folder 10)
      Annual Meeting, Meetings, Incentives, Conventions of America, Inc. (MICA) Services and Disneyland Hotel, correspondence
    - Kerr, S., 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 11)
      Annual Meeting, "B-time" System, correspondence
    - Kerr, S., 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 12)
      Annual Meeting, All-Academy Symposium, correspondence
    - Kerr, S., 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 13)
      Annual Meeting, Greyhound Exposition Services, correspondence
    - Kerr, S., 1987 (Box 8, Folder 14)
      Management Practitioners Task Force, correspondence
    - Kerr, S., 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Kerr, S., 1988-1989 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Kerr, S., 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Kerr, S., 1981 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Koontz, H., 1963 (Box 8, Folder 19)
      Presidential correspondence with the membership, November, 1963
    - Litterer, J., 1970 (Box 8, Folder 20)
      Presidential Newsletter
    - Mee, J., 1952-1954 (Box 8, Folder 21)
      correspondence, includes discussion of membership issues; collecting early records of the Academy; reference list of textbooks and theories of general management
    - Mee, J., 1957 (Box 8, Folder 22)
      establishment of Midwest Division
    - Mee, J., 1958 (Box 8, Folder 23)
      syllabi for seminar entitled "Development of Management Thought,"
    - Miner, J., 1975-1978 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Newsom, W., 1985-1988 (Box 8, Folder 25)
      Board of Governors (BOG), correspondence
    - Newsom, W., 1987-1989 (Box 8, Folder 26)
      Academy of Management (AOM) Handbook revision, correspondence
    - Newsom, W., 1989 (Box 8, Folder 27)
      Annual Meeting, programs, correspondence
    - Newsom, W., 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 28)
      list of officers, representatives, and division chairpersons
    - Newsom, W., 1981-1989 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Newsom, W., 1981-1989 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Newsom, W., 1988-1989 (Box 8, Folder 31)
      Search Committee for new Secretary-Treasurer, correspondence
    - Newsom, W., 1987-1989 (Box 8, Folder 32)
      committees and divisions, correspondence
    - Newsom, W., 1988 (Box 8, Folder 33)
      Meetings, Incentives, Conventions of America, Inc (MICA), correspondence
    - Newsom, W., 1988-1989 (Box 8, Folder 34)
      Budget, correspondence
    - Newsom, W., 1985-1989 (Box 8, Folder 35)
      publications correspondence in role of Business Manager
    - Newsom, W., 1981-1989 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Pledger, R., 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Pledger, R., 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Pledger, R., 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Pledger, R., 1979-1981 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Ray, D., 1976-1979 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Reyer, K., 1935-1959 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Reyer, K., 1961-1990 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Richards, M., 1967 (Box 8, Folder 44)
      presidential correspondence to the membership
    - Schell, E., 1950 (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Slocum, J., 1974 (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Slocum, J., 1982 (Box 8, Folder 47)
      publisher advertising concerns at annual meeting, correspondence
    - Slocum, J., 1982 (Box 8, Folder 48)
      annual meeting doctoral consortia
    - Slocum, J., 1984 (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Smiddy, H., 1962 (Box 8, Folder 50)
      Letter from the President, Fall 1962
    - Steers, R., 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 51)
      Board of Governors (BOG) issues, correspondence
    - Steers, R., 1985-1986 (Box 8, Folder 52)
      Ad-Hoc Committee on Doctoral Student Recruitment, report and correspondence
    - Steers, R., 1986 (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - Terry, G., 1961 (Box 8, Folder 54)
      Letter from the President, Fall 1961
    - Terry, G. (Box 8, Folder 55)
      "Operation 61 for Your Academy of Management." A plan developed by Terry to provide direction for the Academy; the present status of our Academy, the challenges facing our Academy, and the current planning and hoped for goal of our Academy
    - Terry, G., 1962 (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - Terry, G., 1974 (Box 8, Folder 57)
      Institute for Administrative Research (IAR) Board of Directors, correspondence and meeting agendas
    - Terry, G., 1968-1974 (Box 8, Folder 58)
      IAR, correspondence
    - Terry, G., 1970-1974 (Box 8, Folder 59)
      ALCOA Foundation/ IAR, correspondence
    - Terry, G., 1974 (Box 8, Folder 60)
      IAR's break with Academy of Management, correspondence
    - Terry, G., 1973 (Box 8, Folder 61)
      IAR financial records
    - Vance, S., 1976 (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - Wortman, M., 1979-1982 (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - Wortman, M., 1981 (Box 8, Folder 64)
      BOG Meeting, August 5, 1981
    - Wortman, M., 1981 (Box 8, Folder 65)
      BOG Meeting, December 11-13, 1981
    - Wortman, M., 1982 (Box 8, Folder 66)
      BOG Meeting, April 23-24, 1982
    - Wortman, M., 1982 (Box 8, Folder 67)
      BOG Meeting, August 14-15, 1982
    - Wortman, M., 1978 (Box 8, Folder 68)
      Annual Meeting, program evaluations by program chairpersons
    - Wortman, M., 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 69)
      Annual Meetings, program time allocation
    - Wortman, M., 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 70)
      Annual Meetings, hotel contracts
    - Wortman, M., 1979 (Box 8, Folder 71)
      Annual Meeting, pre-registrant list
    - Wortman, M., 1979 (Box 8, Folder 72)
      Annual Meeting, attendance statistics
    - Wortman, M., 1979 (Box 8, Folder 73)
      notes re: Annual Meeting, program operations
    - Wortman, M., 1979 (Box 8, Folder 74)
      Annual Meeting printing requirements
    - Wortman, M., 1980 (Box 8, Folder 75)
      Annual Meeting, Local Arrangements Committee
    - Wortman, M., 1980 (Box 8, Folder 76)
      Annual Meeting, Call for Papers
    - Wortman, M., 1980 (Box 8, Folder 77)
      Annual Meeting, divisional program chairpersons list
    - Wortman, M., 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 78)
      Program Chairpersons, meeting, August 11, 1979
    - Wortman, M., 1980 (Box 8, Folder 79)
      Annual Meeting, memos to program chairpersons
    - Wortman, M., 1980 (Box 8, Folder 80)
    - Wortman, M., 1980 (Box 8, Folder 81)
      Annual Meeting, program suggestions
    - Wortman, M., 1980 (Box 8, Folder 82)
      Annual Meeting, original program copy
    - Wortman, M., 1980 (Box 8, Folder 83)
      Annual Meeting, program matrix
    - Wortman, M., 1980 (Box 8, Folder 84)
      Annual Meeting, program corrections
    - Wortman, M., 1980 (Box 8, Folder 85)
      Annual Meeting, preliminary program, printed
    - Wortman, M., 1980 (Box 8, Folder 86)
      Annual Meeting, final program
    - Wortman, M., 1980 (Box 8, Folder 87)
      Annual Meeting, banquet resume
    - Wortman, M., 1980 (Box 8, Folder 88)
      Annual Meeting, hotel correspondence